(Raj:)And if it's a clear night,
(Raj:)I'm gonna lay
some romantic astronomy on her.
(Penny:)Okay, like what? Show me.
(Raj:)I can't do that to Leonard.
(Raj:)This is some powerful
panty-dropping stuff.
(Leonard:)You have my blessing. Go for it.
(Bernadette:)Okay.
(Raj:)Penny, two of the brightest stars
in the night sky
(Raj:)are Altair and Vega.
(Raj:)And it is said
they were deeply in love
(Raj:)but forever separated by the
celestial river of the Milky Way.
(Penny:)-That's sad.
-It is.
(Raj:)But once a year,
(Raj:)on the seventh day
of the seventh month,
(Raj:)Vega cries so hard that all
the magpies in the world fly up
(Raj:)and create a bridge with their wings
so the two lovers can be together
(Raj:)for a single night of passion.
(Penny:)Wow.